[Applause]
[Music]
for
shock
[Music]
partner and
International
[Music]
Ro
[Applause]
for
um I'd like to
thank
so at Diamond color
[Music]
Institute we have uh 12 levels of
training and tonight the book says third
level but in their life people want
four I think the first one is uh
Financial Independence
[Music]
uh we would like to have enough money
that we don't have to think about
[Music]
money so I I I don't care to be super
wealthy uh but I think everyone would
like to have enough money they don't
have to think about
money so for example now we are sitting
in this h
uh we are breing
oxygen nobody's worried that somebody
else oh here is reading too much
oygen we just feel comfortable we don't
think about
[Music]
it we just
bre and I think money should be like
that our our
income it should be
transparent uh we don't have to think
about
it just money comes in and it's
enough and we feel
comfortable and can take care of our
family I think that's one goal that
everybody in the world
[Music]
shares in my own
experience if you are very
wealthy but your house is
empty you have a big house you have a
big
apartment you come home nobody's there
you cook by cooking by yourself is
very and eating by yourself is
very and then uh you can see some
wealthy
people they they come home to an empty
big empty
house that's a very
Lely
so I don't think it helps to have
money if you don't have
relationships
especially so I was in China South
China we are supposed to be having I
think there were like 3 400 business
people and we are supposed to be talking
about how to make more money in your
business then one ra her
head then yes yeah she said can you use
this diamond C principle for your
husband some other
wait what can you use it for your
wife like uh I guess so I'm A M I don't
know
can then the whole business conference
collapsed nobody wants to talk about
business everybody wants to talk about
their wife or their
husband I thought oh maybe I should talk
about that
sometimes then there's a third goal that
people
uh if you make a lot of
money and if you have a good
relationship but if you don't have
energy if you feel
old like many people they spend their
energy to become
wealthy after they become
wealthy they lost all their
energy then they can't enjoy the money
they can't enjoy their
family they can't enjoy their
life so many business people came to
me teach me to find
partner and then teach me how to
stay how can I have energy like young
[Music]
person can you teach me
that can you use Diamond kind principles
for
that
they you care just come uh then after
you have those three
things you have I call oxygen
money your income Is Like
Oxygen it's
transparent you don't notice
it just money coming I don't have any
record of how much money is coming to
me that's her
problem then uh it just comes just come
down and I don't know how much
there and then I just spend it all all
day I gave money to
people sometimes I call her I said do we
have enough
money yeah we have enough give
more then I just give it he give some
house so to have that kind of money
to have a beautiful
relationships so I I believe I have the
most beautiful relationships I ever saw
in my
life so I have money and I have I have I
think the most beautiful relationship I
can imagine
have
Contin I didn't meet anybody whose
relationship I thought was more
[Music]
beautiful of course you want
energy you want to be able to do many
things be excited about your
life like it's nice to have energy sh
those three things are
nice after you get
that after you have that
and you know how to
get you want to share
other it's
fun uh last night I was
in I'm sitting with investment
bankers telling them how to become more
wealthy and it's for me it's
fun we are like having dinner
together supposed to be like like 50
bankers and after two days more and more
people are
com we are in a
restaurant got one
more at the end it was 130
people asking
questions and that's fun for
me to help other people to go around the
world help the
world I think everybody wants that
we want money we we want sex sex uh we
want to be young we young but
deeper uh we want to be help the whole
world didn't we we like what do you call
spidermanman
iron
[Music]
Transformers Super Wonder Woman Wonder
Woman like that you have all why why are
we so
interested if they make a movie about
superhero everybody will
go it will make a100
million you just have to put another
name in front of
man
woman
exom anything
doesn't all of us want to be like a
superhero
we want to help the
world I think these are the four goals
of all
people uh people want
money not to think about
money then we want a good
partnership nice
family and uh we want to be
young and we want to help the
Home Med so our uh Institute
purpose uh is to give people those four
things help people get those four
things and then we just go around the
world and more and more people invite
us and we
go so we have uh 12 levels of
training uh in those 12 levels
people learn to reach those four
BS so in uh in the world we got to I
don't know we have 156
cities that we have to go to
then then uh actually Hamburg is the
head of all of them hurg is the and I'm
not just saying that it's
true it's because of those three very
they
[Music]
insist they have a they do a
trick they give us a very good
dinner they
what's next
day
this is the first time in the whole
world50
cities that we will do
level uh level
one is how to make oxygen
money how do you have enough
money just so you don't have to sit
level
two is what should I do with my
life some people don't know what they
want to
do they went to
University they
graduate they join a
company they stay in the company for 10
years 20
years during that time they have
family
then they reach 40 years old 50 years
old then they start begin to
think I'm not doing what I wanted to
do some hidden
talent there's something I
want I have a good
job I like
my but but I didn't find the thing which
I
[Music]
L we
finished uh level
three by the way if you didn't do these
three
levels uh you can ask one of those
ladies will be Karm
SP uh those they are
teaching first
three so if you missed one you can you
can
ask they do a couple of weeks they
do just
ask then the third
level is how to
meditate how to concentrate your
mind it's very
beautiful uh it's a 2,000 years old
very beautiful uh drawing
painting and then we do 5 days two days
talk three days
Retreat just about
meditation how to learn
meditation for what how to use
meditation for your
business uh use meditation for your
career
use meditation for your
family uh the person who has a peaceful
mind very clear mind they have better
family and they have better
career so that was Lev
three then it comes
from uh but I don't care what is your
religion doesn't matter to me
few months ago we taught in
Indonesia everybody's
Muslim they really like these
L they go to
China everybody we T
communist I don't I'm not supposed to
wear this
day I have toar tired
and it doesn't matter they
enjoy and they are
successful and they made a lot of
successful people
there so like that in Israel we have
many many groups 21 groups in
isra 35 gr uh I and so it doesn't matter
to me what is your background I don't
care just
successful be
happy so love of four and love of
five these are about
relationships how to have a good
relationship so we will start level four
now uh two nights different
talks first half
tonight second half tomorrow
night we will start
uh how do have a
relationship how do we have a nice
part so what's the difference between
level four and level
five level four is how to find a
relationship how to
[Music]
start how to
find or how to find a
friend how to find your
relationship and a little bit in love of
four we do uh partner
Improvement so some people say I already
have
partner I have partner I have husband
for 20
years every year he gets more
born
uh then we can teach you how to uh
improve
make him more
excited like that there's a list of
things about your husband or your
wife will start
that
level see level four is how to
find how to adjust
that 10 uh love
fire is how to keep
them sometimes you
you and and you can't
keep that's Lev five and
then sometimes you find them and you
keep them but then you're not
happy you meet uh people you say how
long are you
married I had the 20 not to
young like that so it's possible you
keep them but you're not
happy so L
five how to keep that and be
[Music]
happy more happy every
year every year you are
together you are more happy than before
so my my main
relationship it's now uh 42
years uh since we met each
other and every year it's more
amazing more beautiful feel more like a
teenager every
year okay then I can show you how to
make money can tell uh but this is also
something valuable this is
[Music]
uh uh to have money is is good get to
have but to have a beautiful
relationship
life it gets more beautiful
every that's that's also
precious
uh so I would like you to have
both and uh so if you want the
money you have to talk to the
L because now I don't repeat
level there's no
time 12 levels in
156 so we are going now to level four
and we will talk about
relationship okay if you need money you
didn't get oxygen
money
okay people ask me well let me
see I'd like to start with a
meditation uh this is a good meditation
you can
learn it it will teach you to focus
and you can use it for your
job you can use it in your
family it will give you great
peace and great
Focus uh whatever your belief doesn't
matter your mind will be
sharp and
peaceful so that's also my
goal to teach you that
uh so we will start with that if your
mind is
peaceful and
sharp then I teach you how to find a
partner you will understand
faster it's important to put your mind
in a good place
first so I'd like to introduce I brought
about 10
teachers from our Institute from and I'd
like to introduce Kev
[Music]
[Applause]
Mor in
russan for the last five
years and I never heard about
that I also didn't know anybody's
publishing
[Music]
the uh but I was happy
they we have a nice
training about a thousand of the workers
came then on the last day they said the
the owner wants to meet
you the owner of the
company then I I didn't know about him
before but he's one of the wealthiest
people in the
world
he has eight8 billion 8
billion uh then I supposed to go to
dinner with
him and we have to drive for almost two
hours go to some big
hotel then the whole restaurant is
empty only three guys are sitting there
there they're like this I came in
they they watching me and I I asked a
translator who who had
this that's his
bodyguards they looking
[Music]
at
we I know we had nice
din we made plan to go
back then he said I have to go uh see my
family he stood
up then he looked at
me he said you know the most important
thing in in a person's
life they should have a
partner and that part should be sent by
God they should spend their life on
this and and the goal of life is to
become
[Music]
one there's a debate in in
Buddhism uh there is a
practice uh there's a very high kind of
meditation and you're supposed to do
that with a
partner even a mon is supposed to uh
have a
partner then you're supposed to do this
practice
with then that practice is
secret and uh then there in the secret
books they talk about this
practice and uh they have some questions
about
it one
question uh they said a
mon they are supposed to uh they don't
care about physical
attraction we're not supposed to drink
alcohol uh we're not supposed to eat too
much a real mon uh after 12:00 you
cannot
eat so we're not supposed to watch
[Music]
television sometimes in our Monastery
India the young monk he sneaks to the
town to see a
movie and the Indian uh rest
owner they have a secret
room and all the months go there and
they show
movies not bad
movies uh police you know American
police
movies you watch the
movie quiet you s
home to the
monastery then if they catch
you uh they will they will call your
name come on come
on uh in the main
Temple there will be in my Monastery
almost 2000
month so they call you up to
the then they give you big movie
poster uh you know some Indian
movie then you have to stand like
this you have to hold the
must one
hour if the arm comes
down then they they will hit
you then of course we think of Monk
physically a monk shouldn't be attracted
to these things and
like a lot of good
food big
car or or a
lady we shouldn't be attracted to
them physically physically and then
mentally we shouldn't have desire for
those things so we
can we're not supposed to meditate about
Mercedes
Benz mercedesz or uh some
girl you know we're not supposed to
we're not mentally we're not supposed to
think about this
thing phally we're not supposed to do
this then when you get very
high in the
practice you're supposed to have
partner then the question
comes when are you supposed to have a
[Music]
is it after after you don't have desire
or or before it's
[Music]
okay then it's a big debate in in the
scriptures because you're supposed to
have
[Music]
your there are four secret
permissions
uh that you have to have from your
[Music]
teacher number three is to have a
partner and practice
with so then they ask a
question at what
stage is it okay
[Music]
to when is when is you don't want
partner you have no
desire
in your mind physically also you don't
want to do those
things what stage do you reach
time big debate in the
scripture the answer is very
beautiful they said uh when you have
enough
love for
humankind then you can have a
problem when you have love for the
world then you should have a it doesn't
matter about it's not a question of you
want those
things or your body you feel like
[Music]
those if you reach
love for the world then you should have
a partner that's then that becomes
confusing
how does the teacher
know when you are ready for uh number
three they call permission number
three is to
have and they said how does the teacher
know that the monke is
ready and they they have a very
beautiful
answer uh when you reach the place the
Buddha
reached then they have long beautiful
story so maybe you heard how the Buddha
became
in Buddha was a
prince Buddha had billions of
dollars then uh one day he saw a dead
man and he asked his friend
what's wrong with
him he's dead
then why not why everyone
dies I also have to
die yeah it doesn't matter you're king
or he R
away then he meditated for many
years then uh he went to there's a town
in in India called
bod noway
called at that time it was
called seat of the
diamond they say he sat under the
special tree right
tree he did final
meditation then he
became then in the secret
books they said no no no it wasn't
my that was just uh
play he's just
pretending he got in long time
before millions of
years then they say you want to know the
real
story then you're like you're like
looking
at what's the
then uh they say he was uh
meditating he was almost became
Buddha but he couldn't something stoping
him and he couldn't reach
Enlightenment and that was in the
evening then he got
stuck then he's sitting there very
frustrated then they say many
Buddhas many other
Buddhas how to make him a
Buddha he has
obstacle
need he has to
practice so they b a
angel Special
Angel her name
is
you should know her
name she made the
Buddha her name is like nobody
knows means like tilopa it means Sesame
small small
[Music]
Drop Like
Honey or uh nectar or a nectar nectar in
Greek means NE means
die me to
Cross nectar means one
drop of
that
take then you don't have to
die so her
name is
me one
drop means highest
so her means
High next was
midnight the Clock Struck
midnight
then they brought her to
him and they said you have to practice
with
her then he he
start then uh for like four
hours uh they start
together and uh he feels her
energy the he has a man's
energy she has a woman's
energy then the two energies start to
mix
together then what he is lacking that's
what in she has what she is lacking
he has he needs her energy energy and
she needs his
energyy and then the energy start to uh
combine they said
uh when the Sun starts to we call day
break not Dawn Dawn means Sun you can
see the sun Day means starts to get
light in um Sun didn't break
then because of
the so it's like 4:00
5:00 in the
morning then their energy is
mixing and that energy has connection to
the
Sun so the light start to
come and they are both feeling uh LIF
from each
other then they they going because of
the
Bliss they start to go into very deep
meditation and and that meditation
changes the
sun and the Sun starts to get brighter
and
brighter Sun starts to break the
Horizon then they reach
special meditation called clear clear
light
then both together they reach this deep
meditation called
CLE because of
the so the bless causes
the then they start to
rise then the body start to change
his body and her
body uh because of the
meditation uh both body
changed then the Sun is up the
sun in the first moment of the
F their body
is and they are made of
life in the next
second in the next
second thousands hundreds of thousands
of bodies split from their
body like a
mirror thousands and thousands of bodies
thousand and thousand then those bodies
appear on other
worlds throughout the
sky in the night
sky you can see millions of
stars in the second
moment their body
split and they are
together countless
[Music]
Planet
Ang it's a very beautiful
story then one body came to this world
and pretend to
become under the
tree that was just
pretend they finished a long time
before so that that four
hours that they are
together that became the third
permission
that uh your
teacher must give a
Mone it's
called then since that
time 2 and a half thousand years
ago there has been a
custom when the monk is ready
they will have the thir
commission what does it mean
ready it means
uh in my
case why
I because of the death of my like death
of my mother and my father my
brother my mother
was
and then she
died I I was so
hurt I thought why should a good person
die and my whole mind got
confused then I went to
India I start to
notice poor
people one day in
India I went in
1973 and at that time it was
worse I saw one man he's on the
lawn and he's feating the
grass like a
cow because he has no
food I I'm only
young I looked at him and I said oh this
is terrible
this is it
possible to change
that is it possible that the whole world
could have enough
food if you start to think like
that then you are ready for
part that's the
motivation it doesn't matter how how you
think about pizza speak Pizza things
what do you want
those are small
things do you want to help other
people then you should have
a and
finally all
relationships with
partner you will reach a higher
spiritual
level if you uh have a good
relationship if you learn how to have a
relationship you can have
romance great
romance it's like uh Dante and V so D or
like Jesus and Mary or Jesus
J Mary this is a famous
Romance
you can have
Rance and you will
be like high high
romance what you think
about you can have but if you learn it
the way we are going to
teach you can have a beautiful
apartment you can have a good
family and that relationship
will serve the whole
world will help the whole world so it's
like a higher
relationship and that's what we're going
to
teach some people say it's too
late I already have my husband he he's
never going to be like
that that's not
true okay if you already have a
relationship
you can change it and you can make it
higher if you don't have
Rel you can find
it so it's not too late for
anybody you can have some beautiful
higher
relationship and that's what we're going
to talk
about two nights here first half night
has
second
half then 3 days Retreat Retreat I heard
the retreat is full I heard it sold
out I want you to try to find another
hotel something okay they're going to
have a heart
attack maybe people can stay
nearby so that's your problem this is
okay uh but uh we should have more
SP we work it out
we yeah dear and
dear nice meeting
you I have
and I beg you to please help
me since years I am
lonely and I really wish to have a nice
wonderful beautiful
partner that is not a problem at all
that's you only have to go
to
because these places were invented to
find
[Music]
Parkers uh this is a bad
idea very bad
idea I will tell you why
okay uh the boy that goes to the
nightclub is the kind of boy who go to
the
night
so he will call you from work and he
will tell you that he needs to stay
late but actually we still keep going to
the
night so you don't want it such a boy
right so I will tell you what to
do there are many many online website
for
[Music]
taking okay we just need to go on theet
the internet that's such a
nonsense if you find a guy on the
internet the only you see him is the
of because he will be on Facebook all
the time you will never spend time with
you
don't you w the from
the
[Music]
no I'm so
confused I really want to find a
part but I don't know
where
them I heard about this great new
website where there's guys where you
sign up and you get pictures of them
[Music]
and and then you can meet
all
[Music]
the other person said no no you
shouldn't go to
night you should check on the
internet now it's
start it will take uh 5
days to decide what to
do but let's
begin sometimes when you go on the
internet you can find a nice
partner sometimes when you go on
internet you don't
find sometimes when you go to the
club you find a
nice sometimes when you go to the
club you don't
find
right it's correct great everybody knows
that
therefore going to
club and going to the
internet will not bring you a
partner
also going on
internet going to the
will so people love this kind of
thing you can find
at also you can't
find but to to make it
simple if the internet works sometimes
and it doesn't work
[Music]
sometimes then it doesn't
work I can give the example of a
c
if you have if you buy a new
car three days a week it
starts four days a week it doesn't
start is this a good
car
no if you go to the
club sometimes you find a
GU and sometimes you don't find
a then going to the club is not the
cause of finding a
guy
there must be a deeper
C okay to understand
that what you make
money it's the
same my Lama asked me to start a
company we will feed the
refugees with the money then I said I I
don't like
business he said shut
up yor start
business I don't like business and I
hate New
York let
meay why do you think I
came also in New York when you start bus
it should be
di know like that's even
worse
Diamond all diam people are are bad
people very
greedy they always cheating
people you want me to go to the worst
city join the worst
business be with the worst
people
yes for one almost one year I didn't
go but he pushed me
uh I
went he said we will do
experiment do you understand Karm Karm
so you all know
Karma you heard the word Karma have this
Karm but in the monastery we study karma
for 25
years it's a lot of
details a lot of technique about
teque you go to New York start a
business you make $1 million in one
yearor as an
experiment see do you
understand compan now is 250
million per year and two years ago it
has 10,000
workers uh 3 years ago War
B
uh then we we use some Karma
principles to
make those
principles you can
[Music]
use you can use those
principles then don't be satisfied
[Music]
without
a like the Buddha Buddha if you meet a
grand
partner you can change the
world if you understand how to have a
deep
relationship deep spiritual
relationship with your
you very
beautiful very
important but you have to understand the
principles how to
[Music]
find and it's the same principles which
we use for
business so I want to teach you those
principles you can find a
beautiful or you can change the part you
have and that relationship can become a
high high
relationship and it will serve the whole
world and you will also be extremely
help so that's a
goal uh I will
just and then we take a
break so uh you have to
focus during this five
minut we will begin
with the
principal then uh for 5 days we will
work
on but uh I just want you to know the
first
principle we teach this principle in
every DCI
number they already did it three times
in
my the staff traveling with
me
all the coaches coaches uh if I take out
this
pen to start to explain those
principl they fall
asep because they heard
5000 I don't
care he
[Music]
again learn how to teach it learn
if you already heard
this watch how to teach
it
why if I can teach you to find a holy
High
partner or if I can teach you how to
change your relationship now to become a
[Music]
ho
which will help the whole
world and which will make you so
happy whole life feels like a
miracle if I can show you
that in in
days then you can show somebody
else then you should show somebody
else so so from from this moment this
moment watch how to teach it
don't fall
asleep here we
go what is this
thing don't be like British
[Music]
people if I ask a question you have to
answer what is this
thing
yeah now question if a dog comes in
here comes down the
stairs
do did I show this thing
to what what will the dog
do does the puppy dog see sit and as
no they don't
understand they just see something
to human sees it as
a the dog
as question for
you who's
correct a good answer of course both in
America they say animal
rights
the uh the human little tell the dog
you're a very bad dog you you ruined my
pen
the don't a
good and the dog will say to the
human why are youing with that to it
tastes
great are
correct human is
correct now important
question if you want to find a beautiful
partner or if you want to change your
relationship to something beautiful and
high and
romantic it's High Hope holy
very okay it's everything you have to
you have to understand the next
thing if I take this
pen if I put it
here then I chase out all the
humans I tell them there are
Refreshments outside let
keep everybody
will then if I kick out the
dog no humans
here
dogs at that
time is this a
or which
one
NE if the human comes back
first it will become
a if the dog comes in
first it will
become am
I am I right
yeah
therefore can we
say this thing is coming from me from
me yeah you have to
say the pen is not coming from the
pen if the pen is coming from the pen
then the dog will try to ride some
home to his dog
girlfriend you have nice
[Music]
but he
doesn't because the pen is not a
from when a human
com they see
a it must be coming from the human
mind
how then uh
you can close your
eyes you can say I don't want a
p i want a bar of
gold if it's coming from
me then I don't want
to I
[Music]
want
oh you can also do monke
[Music]
then then if it's coming from
me it should
be it's still
there it's coming from my
mind but I cannot change
it by thinking of something
else there's a
power
my it's like a SE in my and that seed
causes it forces me to
see and the dog has a different
SE the dog
see
for to
and so how do the seed get in my
mind how did his seed get in his mind
I'll show you
fast why are we talking about
this
partner coming from you from here okay
and how you see your
partner my
partner list to
me
always doesn't wash
dishes it's all coming from you
if you understand the
process you can
change you can make them
beautiful
you so how to the
se you cannot plant a seed by yourself
it's not
possible you need another
person it's like they are the ground and
you are the F you so the
without the ground you can't plant a
seed they like the
ground then what is the
SE
then find a person let's say I want
a I'm looking
for
like is looking
for she's looking in the
nightcloud she's looking on the internet
you know but he cannot F then in this
system we
[Music]
say don't worry about don't worry about
looking in
night looking
online don't waste your
time why sometimes it works and
sometimes it doesn't so that means it
doesn't
work
said don't don't do those
things they don't
work what do you want me
[Music]
to when you meet your partner it's going
to come from
you
so take
control
make don't look for them make them and
so again create them that's much safer
see can make the way
you okay so let's
say I don't
know he
wants so I want
to I need to find another person who
[Music]
wants and I
find he tells me I'm looking for
like Mercedes when she came
here she asked the other
please said let's go to
Starbucks Starbucks it's very important
to do that
stbu because that's the last great
American
company economy needs some
more okay
so I tell
him he's looking I must find someone
who's looking
for I must
tell let's go
to I I will help you we can talk
together I'm also looking
for let's go to
St and and we can help each
other when I say that I hear myself
talking you
hear that makes a recording in my
mind it puts a SE in my mind
sh maybe 3 weeks
later I'm sitting in St
alone I I helped him
to door
opens some beautiful l
I'm she comes to
my
sit in this system there are no
accidents everything
has you talk to people how did you meet
your
husband how did you meet your wife many
people will say it was
accident I was on the bus where are we
here today
um oh we stayed last night in
z uh we asked the husband how he met the
wife they said we met in the
art said what
happened then they said the wife got in
L for the to
admission then the
the husband got in L behind
her then he he said to her excuse
me I have two
tickets and she said I'm the director of
the
museum each
other it's easy 30 seconds
slower to come out of the
taxi people never meet her it's like
they have two beautiful
children
sayd there's
noci don't wait for
accidents you plant a SE
how help somebody else who looking for
help take
to
support later you will be sitting you be
waiting in line at
Museum and the guy would say I have
two then when
why did he come at that
moment in the mind there is no
accident everything has a
CA so we have to find that
cause we have to
[Music]
create we'll talk for after break i'
like all the stuff
teach
[Music]
yeah who
else ER these people they traveled with
me uh some of them live in
[Music]
h i trained
them for many
years uh are very good about money
making
things they very good about boyfriend
[Music]
Mak sa the
world and uh if you have question during
the talk to
them okay they are here for you for five
days they're just here to to help
you uh then I'll stay here if you want
to also
C
tonight
very okay see you 15 minut
[Music]
I went in the kitchen you K
500 she said she just in the
kitchen she SKS lonely she she doesn't
like to go in the kitchen she get in the
kit I spent almost three four
hours clean her kitchen
uh people feel
Lely so step number
two make a plan I will have a
question for example old
people often
times so make a
plan to help
somebody then step number
three help them okay step number two are
imag how
you step number
[Music]
three bring
flow
will
for step number
four when you go
home after that then think about
it what you do to help
them okay then
tomorrow I will teach you the
details of the four
steps then step number
three is planting the
seed that's a good
thing but if you don't know how to put
the water
fertilizer farming
technique mental seed plantic
technique if you don't know
how that seed will not
grow you can put SE
here and if you don't take care of the
seed it won't
grow so we have to study the four steps
together tomorrow we miss
how
to se how to get the SE
grow you don't have to be
lonely nobody has to be
lonely anybody can
plant it doesn't matter what your age
is this it doesn't matter what you look
[Music]
like if you plant the
there's no reason to be
lonely there's no reason if you
want there's no reason
to just learn how
to the years of your
life they
passing you are losing every year
you then you shouldn't be alone
you shouldn't wait a long
time without a part that woman who who
came home to her home
she I feel so bad for
her I know how to find her
partner uh she has to
PL I can show her how to
plant but she won't
listen she won't
try she just lives like
that she's getting
older and I feel sad for
her it's not necessary to
be it's not necessary to
be just learn how
to some people they feel
shy where am I going to find that
a
man I'm 40 I'm
[Music]
5050 you know I don't want to go
to I feel stupid to
go I want
to but I I don't know how to meet
them and I I'm a shy
person I don't I don't talk to people
easily who are
strangers also I got
hurt in my life many people I was
married before
they I had a
problem and now I'm
afraid I don't want to try have
part in this system you can't forget
those it doesn't matter what happened
before it doesn't matter your
age and even if you are
shy in this system you don't have to
talk
to you don't have to go to
Club you don't have to go on the
internet just plant the
SE and
relax it's like
uh
water uh you plant the
SE and there's no
ST just plant the seed plant the then
relax it will grow it will come and you
don't have to do anything you don't have
to look on the
internet you don't have to go to the
club just PL
the will come
beautiful
kind
affection they will come and it just
relax him I would teach you
tomorrow four STS to
plant just PL don't Rel you will
come I recently I went to a yoga class
yoga CL I finished my business in
1999 I didn't work in the D
business I planted the seeds for
money money comes to me now it comes to
me without
buiness people say h I say okay I went
to
class in New York New York uh the
teacher
heard great
teacher he does
without he's 72 years old
he's
72 then he's one of my
teachers I went to his
class then after the class one guy came
to
me my name is John I want you to shake
your hand I said nice to meet
you I said I have to go
now I went home then I after the next
day I got an Emil
it's from John John I don't know how he
got it's
[Music]
not he said why didn't you
me I didn't know what he's talking
about I
said
for then he sent me email
again look in your in your
B I always carry
this then he said you
look I looked
inside there's
envelope I
open inside to check and Che $100,000
$1,000
I
thank you thank you thank
you then I said you don't know me you CH
me why you believe this
Mone I said I don't know why I just want
to give
you and I said what am I supposed to
do
what where did they come
from why did I me
him there's no
accident I pled
[Music]
it just comes
so without
anxiety without
stress I will teach you tomorrow for
St just
like maybe in the line at
mum uh so the last thing I'd like to do
tonight there's
a one of the teachers here in
h her name
is she's going to teach us
[Music]
number